overview
chance
ability
perspective
From perspective to Nils Ferlin:
The wind is grievous,
The cold string:
Please be good for a small stable!
For he wishes something for his own part
Is it just a Magdeburg game.
That would he finger little songs on
that would all the parish with astonishment beating.
And people would travel in miles and more
To hear his handkind.
Vregig is the wind, the cold string:
He curves up,
Our stable.
However, soon he will sit in highness large
And snap on buttons of pearl.
Then it will be to say at mill and crusher:
A strange man!
- An acquaintance to us.
Yes he went here and froze just like us.
- A great genius
So it could sometimes fall a word.
- Although air is air and soil
so that it is likely that our stable bang freezes stiff
in the cold string.
Freezes themselves - just like we,
And never get big and famous and free.
Without just allowed to go there -
day after day,
It became quite quiet in the village:
Denied the comet proved his place in the sky
For the whole congregation!
Portent
said one to the end
- A racker to shine!
- -
Now the grace time was blown out,
Now it's time to think!
Now is the time to shop right
toward the mor- and fatherless,
and garde in every way
And be religious.
So they set out with speed at glasses and postillas
and sighed so heavy and rare
About the world's wreck conditions.
They bowed for poorjon as before for thick stomachs
and weighed right in the trading residence
for almost 14 days
They looked at the almanac's leaves in sproutingly surprised,
Until someone came one day and sad:
Now it's even a month.
Among other things this, "Ich bin Gewen A Mol A Jingling"
"I was once a youngster"
(song on Yiddish)
I was once a youngster
heard Socrates in the arcades
and my soul mate, my darling
Had the most beautiful Torson in Athens.
Yes Caesar
And a bright world built of marble.
I, the last
And to wife I chose out
My proud sister.
In rose wreath with wine until late
I heard with highly calm about the waving from Nazareth
and wild stories about Jews
(song on Yiddish)
From Margolin to Andersson:
Now the spring's lukewarm winds
In the Yellow's Yellow Star,
And slowly rise the fairy tales around the island in Berga Fors.
Forgive a splash of bitter joy,
a show to guitar,
The strong us to healing
Like the young pores of the beach.
A song to you, my sister,
When all the ground awaits ours!
But lovely,
Lovely spring came every year in roses dressed,
Although the twilight of the grief sought us and bleached the color of the cheek.
A day on knees for the king,
one night for the shadow scared,
and then you drank bliss
out of river and mountains and mountains.
Come out,
When the storm winds wild in Apel, Arrow and Hägg!
See, spring heavens burn
To the praise of God and stars!
And when you are anesthetized to dreams
of the resented at your wall,
All the roses of meadows shout,